Register of the Robert Charles Hill papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Robert Charles Hill papers
1929-1978
79067
Hoover Institution Archives
183 manuscript boxes, 29 scrapbooks, 73 envelopes, 4 oversize boxes, 9 motion picture film reels, 4 sound tape reels (93.7 linear feet)
Speeches and writings, correspondence, reports, clippings, other printed matter, photographs, motion picture film, and sound recordings relating to conditions in and American relations with Latin America and Spain, American foreign policy and domestic politics, and the Republican Party. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Hill, Robert Charles, 1917-1978
Access
Collection is open for research. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items, computer media, and digital files. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos, films, or digital files during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1979.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Alternate Forms Available
Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Biographical Note
1917 September 30 Born, Littleton, New Hampshire
1941-1944 Washington, D.C., representative, New England Shipbuilding Corporation
1944-1945 U.S. Vice Consul, Calcutta, India
1947 Clerk, U.S. Senate Banking and Currency Committee
1947-1949 Washington, D.C., representative, National Confectioners Association
1949-1953 Assistant Vice President, W. R. Grace and Company
1953-1954 U.S. Ambassador to Costa Rica
1954-1955 U.S. Ambassador to El Salvador
1955-1956 Special Assistant to the U.S. Undersecretary of State for Mutual Security Affairs
1956-1957 U.S. Assistant Secretary of State for Congressional Relations
1957-1961 U.S. Ambassador to Mexico
1961-1962 New Hampshire State Representative
1965-1968 Chairman, Foreign Policy Task Force, Republican National Committee
1969-1972 U.S. Ambassador to Spain
1973-1974 U.S. Assistant Secretary of Defense for International Security Affairs
1974-1977 U.S. Ambassador to Argentina
1978 November 28 Died, Littleton, New Hampshire
Scope and Content of Collection
The Robert Charles Hill papers contain materials relating to conditions in and U.S. foreign relations with Latin America and Spain as well as American foreign policy, domestic policy, and the Republican party.
Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ); United States. Department of State.; Argentina--Foreign relations--United States.; Audiotapes.; Diplomats--United States.; Latin America--Foreign relations--United States.; Mexico--Foreign relations--United States.; Motion pictures.; Spain--Foreign relations--United States.; United States--Armed Forces.; United States--Foreign relations--Argentina.; United States--Foreign relations--Latin America.; United States--Foreign relations--Mexico.; United States--Foreign relations--Spain.; United States--Politics and government--1945-1989.
- Early Life File, 1929-1946
  Scope and Content note
  Correspondence, clippings, and printed matter, arranged by form.
  - Correspondence, 1929-1946
    - Adams, Sherman, 1946 (Box-folder 1: 1)
    - Ananio, Vito, undated (Box-folder 1: 2)
    - Andrews, W. G., 1944 (Box-folder 1: 3)
    - Bennett, William R., Jr., 1942 (Box-folder 1: 4)
    - Blaik, Earl H., 1939 (Box-folder 1: 5)
    - Boston University Law School, 1946 (Box-folder 1: 6)
    - Dartmouth College, 1946 (Box-folder 1: 7)
    - Duden, H. R., 1943 (Box-folder 1: 8)
    - Gorman, Ernest, undated (Box-folder 1: 9)
    - Harrison, Ted, 1937 (Box-folder 1: 10)
    - Hill, Dr. and Mrs. A. F., 1932-1939 (Box-folder 1: 11)
    - Hill, Jack, undated (Box-folder 1: 12)
    - Hill, Richard, 1939 (Box-folder 1: 13)
    - Kennison, Mason, 1937 (Box-folder 1: 14)
    - Mackin, John J., undated (Box-folder 1: 15)
    - Miller, Whit, undated (Box-folder 1: 16)
    - Morse, Mrs. K. C., 1939 (Box-folder 1: 17)
    - Reisinger, W. U., 1938 (Box-folder 1: 18)
    - Rutgers University. Alumni Association, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 1: 19)
    - Shee, Bill, 1938 (Box-folder 1: 20)
    - Sides, Andrew B., 1943 (Box-folder 1: 21)
    - Skilton, Raymond, 1936 (Box-folder 1: 22)
    - Smith, Margaret Chase, 1943 (Box-folder 1: 23)
    - Sterling, John C., 1938 (Box-folder 1: 24)
    - Taft School, 1938 (Box-folder 1: 25)
    - Tilton School, 1937 (Box-folder 1: 26)
    - Tobey, Charles W., 1943 (Box-folder 1: 27)
    - Twentieth Century Fox, 1944 (Box-folder 1: 28)
    - Unidentified, 1929-1938 (Box-folder 1: 29)
    - Varma, S. N., 1946 (Box-folder 1: 30)
  - Miscellany. Clippings, poems, and notes, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 1: 31)
  - Subject file, 1930-1946
    - New England Shipbuilding Corporation, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 1: 32)
      - Correspondence, 1942-1943
        - General, 1942-1943
          - American Bronze Company, 1942 (Box-folder 1: 32)
          - Central Iron and Steel Company, 1942 (Box-folder 1: 33)
          - Chesebro, Whitman Company, 1942 (Box-folder 1: 34)
          - Churchill, Chester L., 1943 (Box-folder 1: 35)
          - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company, 1942 (Box-folder 1: 36)
          - Hill, Roland F., 1942 (Box-folder 1: 37)
          - Lovell-Dressel Company, 1942 (Box-folder 1: 38)
          - Marden, Ford, 1942 (Box-folder 1: 39)
          - National Malleable and Steel Castings Company, 1942 (Box-folder 1: 40)
          - Pinkham, T. B., 1943 (Box-folder 1: 41)
          - Sturtevant (B. F.) Company, 1942 (Box-folder 1: 42)
          - United States Rubber Company, 1942 (Box-folder 1: 43)
          - Upson-Walton Company, 1942 (Box-folder 1: 44)
          - Walworth Company, 1942 (Box-folder 1: 45)
        - Outgoing, 1942-1943
          - 1942 April (Box-folder 1: 46)
          - 1943 June (Box-folder 1: 47)
      - Miscellany. Pamphlet, map, organization charts, and memoranda, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 1: 48)
    - Schools, 1930-1947
      - Clippings, 1934-1947 (Box-folder 1: 49-50)
      - Clippings, 1934-1947 (Box-folder 2: 1)
      - Miscellany. Programs, certificates, and examinations, 1930-1939 (Box-folder 2: 2)
    - U.S. Department of State, 1939-1946
      - Correspondence, 1944-1946
        - Acheson, Dean, 1945 (Box-folder 2: 3)
        - Hill, Dr. and Mrs. A. F., 1945 (Box-folder 2: 4)
        - Lionel Edwards Company, 1945 (Box-folder 2: 5)
        - McGeary, Stanley A., 1945 (Box-folder 2: 6)
        - Myers, M. S., 1945 (Box-folder 2: 7)
        - Sides, Andrew B., 1944 (Box-folder 2: 8)
        - Stettinius, E. R., Jr., 1944 (Box-folder 2: 9)
        - U.S. Army. Forces, India-Burma Theater, 1945 (Box-folder 2: 10)
        - U.S. Department of State. Division of Finance, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 2: 11)
        - U.S. Department of State. Division of Foreign Service Personnel, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 2: 12)
        - U.S. Government Despatch Agency, 1945 (Box-folder 2: 13)
      - Guide books, 1939-1945 (Box-folder 2: 14-15)
    - U.S. Selective Service System. Letters and applications, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 2: 16)
    - Wedding. Clippings, 1945 (Box-folder 2: 17)
- U.S. Senate Committee on Banking and Currency File, 1946-1952
  Correspondence, clippings, minutes, memoranda, and printed matter, arranged by form.
  - Clippings, 1947 (Box-folder 2: 18)
  - Correspondence, 1946-1947
    - American Export Lines, 1947 (Box-folder 2: 19)
    - Beasley, Robert S., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 20)
    - Bodfish, Morton, 1947 (Box-folder 2: 21)
    - Boston University Law School, 1946 (Box-folder 2: 22)
    - Bricker, John W., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 23)
    - Buck, C. Douglass, 1947 (Box-folder 2: 24)
    - Cain, Harry P., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 25)
    - Capehart, Homer E., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 26)
    - Cortright, Frank W., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 27)
    - Donaldson, Ray S., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 28)
    - Eccles, M. S., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 29)
    - Ellingson, C. H., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 30)
    - Erickson, John L., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 31)
    - Fitzpatrick, B. T., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 32)
    - Flanders, Ralph E., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 33)
    - Foley, Raymond M., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 34)
    - Fulbright, J. W., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 35)
    - Goodloe, John D., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 36)
    - Harl, Maple T., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 37)
    - Heald, Walter N., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 38)
    - Huntington, Ellery C., Jr., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 39)
    - Johnston, Victor A., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 40)
    - McNeill, Warren, 1947 (Box-folder 2: 41)
    - Martin, William McC., Jr., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 42)
    - Maybank, Burnet R., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 43)
    - Myer, D. S., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 44)
    - Needham, Delos J., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 45)
    - Richards, Dexter, 1947 (Box-folder 2: 46)
    - Robertson, A. Willis, 1947 (Box-folder 2: 47)
    - Sparkman, John, 1947 (Box-folder 2: 48)
    - Spingarn, Stephen J., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 49)
    - Stevens, Lewis M., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 50)
    - Thomas, Irving W., 1947 (Box-folder 2: 51)
    - Tobey, Charles W., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 3: 1)
    - Unidentified, 1947 (Box-folder 3: 2)
    - U.S. Comptroller of the Currency, 1947 (Box-folder 3: 3)
    - U.S. Department of State, Division of Central Services, 1947 (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - Job description, undated (Box-folder 3: 5)
  - Legislative calendar, 1947 (Box-folder 3: 6)
  - Minutes of meetings, 1947 (Box-folder 3: 7)
  - Reconstruction Finance Corporation - Loans to Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1947-1952
    - Correspondence, 1947-1951
      - Buck, C. Douglass, 1947 (Box-folder 3: 8)
      - Capehart, Homer E., 1947-1951 (Box-folder 3: 9)
      - Dean, Arthur H., 1947 (Box-folder 3: 10)
      - Flanders, Ralph E., 1947 (Box-folder 3: 11)
      - Fulbright, J. W., 1947 (Box-folder 3: 12)
      - Goodloe, John D., 1947 (Box-folder 3: 13)
      - McCarthy, Joseph R., 1947 (Box-folder 3: 14)
      - Maybank, Burnet R., 1947 (Box-folder 3: 15)
      - Snodgrass, Russell L., 1947 (Box-folder 3: 16)
      - Taylor, Glen H., 1947 (Box-folder 3: 17)
      - Tobey, Charles W., 1947 (Box-folder 3: 18)
      - Unidentified, 1947 (Box-folder 3: 19)
      - U.S. Supreme Court Library, 1947 (Box-folder 3: 20)
    - Memoranda, 1947-1952 (Box-folder 3: 21)
    - Miscellany. Press releases, depositions, and minutes of meetings, 1947-1951 (Box-folder 3: 22)
    - Printed matter, 1945-1951
      - Hearing transcripts, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 3: 23-24)
      - Miscellany. Reports, and clippings, 1947-1951 (Box-folder 3: 25)
- Business Years File, 1946-1953
  Correspondence, clippings, and memoranda, arranged by form.
  - Address books, undated (Box-folder 4: 1-2)
  - Biographical sketches, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 4: 3)
  - Clippings, 1947-1953 (Box-folder 4: 4)
  - Correspondence, 1946-1953
    - General, 1946-1953
      - Adams, Sherman, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 4: 5)
      - Aiken, Paul, 1950 (Box-folder 4: 6)
      - Alexander, Archibald S., 1952 (Box-folder 4: 7)
      - Anderson, Robert B., 1953 (Box-folder 4: 8)
      - Andrews, Bert, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 4: 9)
      - Araujo, Antonio M., 1952 (Box-folder 4: 10)
      - Arey, Hawthorne, 1947 (Box-folder 4: 11)
      - Austin, Guy O., 1953 (Box-folder 4: 12)
      - Baldrige, H. M., 1949-1951 (Box-folder 4: 13)
      - Bartlett, N. T., 1949 (Box-folder 4: 14)
      - Beazlie, Frank, 1951 (Box-folder 4: 15)
      - Beckworth, Lindley, 1952 (Box-folder 4: 16)
      - Beers, Robert M., 1948 (Box-folder 4: 17)
      - Berckemeyer, Fernando, 1952 (Box-folder 4: 18)
      - Bettinghaus, H. W., 1947 (Box-folder 4: 19)
      - Bodfish, Morton, 1947 (Box-folder 4: 20)
      - Bone, Myron R., 1947 (Box-folder 4: 21)
      - Bowdoin, W. Graham, Jr., 1949 (Box-folder 4: 22)
      - Bricker, John W., 1947-1949 (Box-folder 4: 23)
      - Bridges, Styles, 1951-1953 (Box-folder 4: 24)
      - Brill, Herbert B., 1947 (Box-folder 4: 25)
      - Buck, C. Douglass, 1947-1951 (Box-folder 4: 26)
      - Burleson, Omar, 1953 (Box-folder 4: 27)
      - Burr, Jorge, 1952 (Box-folder 4: 28)
      - Butler, John Marshall, 1953 (Box-folder 4: 29)
      - Cain, Harry P., 1949-1952 (Box-folder 4: 30)
      - Calmer, Dick, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 4: 31)
      - Capehart, Homer E., 1951-1953 (Box-folder 4: 32)
      - Capehart, Irma, undated (Box-folder 4: 33)
      - Carlyle, F. Ertel, 1952 (Box-folder 4: 34)
      - Castle, W. R., 1949 (Box-folder 4: 35)
      - Chapman, H. R., 1949-1950 (Box-folder 4: 36)
      - Clapp, Gordon R., 1947 (Box-folder 4: 37)
      - Colby, J. H., 1947 (Box-folder 4: 38)
      - Cole, Albert M., 1953 (Box-folder 4: 39)
      - Colladay, Edward F., 1952 (Box-folder 4: 40)
      - Cotton, Norris, 1948-1952 (Box-folder 4: 41)
      - Creedon, Frank R., 1947 (Box-folder 4: 42)
      - Crosser, Robert, 1952 (Box-folder 4: 43)
      - Cruikshank, Paul, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 4: 44)
      - Danaher, John A., 1951 (Box-folder 4: 45)
      - Davis, Sherlock, 1949 (Box-folder 4: 46)
      - Defense Orientation Conference Association, 1952 (Box-folder 4: 47)
      - Delapena, H. V., 1950 (Box-folder 4: 48)
      - DeMott, Helen, 1952 (Box-folder 4: 49)
      - Denny, Harmar D., 1953 (Box-folder 4: 50)
      - Dewey, S. H., 1951 (Box-folder 4: 51)
      - Diamond, Norman, 1949 (Box-folder 4: 52)
      - Doll, Harry Lee, 1949 (Box-folder 4: 53)
      - Donaldson, Ray S., 1948-1949 (Box-folder 4: 54)
      - Duggan, William F., Jr., 1951 (Box-folder 4: 55)
      - Durham, Richard C., 1949 (Box-folder 4: 56)
      - Eager, Auville, 1949 (Box-folder 4: 57)
      - Eames, Jack, 1949 (Box-folder 4: 58)
      - Eastman, Clinton W., 1947 (Box-folder 4: 59)
      - Eccles, M. S., 1947-1950 (Box-folder 4: 60)
      - Elton, Reuel W., 1949 (Box-folder 4: 61)
      - Elvove, Joseph T., 1949-1951 (Box-folder 4: 62)
      - Evans, Jack K., 1951 (Box-folder 4: 63)
      - Fahey, John H., 1947 (Box-folder 4: 64)
      - Feeney, Joseph G., 1953 (Box-folder 4: 65)
      - Fleming, Philip B., 1950 (Box-folder 4: 66)
      - Fletcher, Samuel, 1947 (Box-folder 4: 67)
      - Floyd, John Paul, 1952 (Box-folder 4: 68)
      - Foley, Kenneth W., 1951 (Box-folder 4: 69)
      - Foley, Raymond M., 1947 (Box-folder 4: 70)
      - Fowler, Henry P., 1949 (Box-folder 4: 71)
      - Frank, Curtiss E., 1947 (Box-folder 4: 72)
      - Freer, Robert Elliott, 1949 (Box-folder 4: 73)
      - Fulbright, J. W., 1947 (Box-folder 4: 74)
      - Garcia, Louis J., 1951 (Box-folder 5: 1)
      - Giannini, L. M., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 2)
      - Gillette, Guy M., 1951 (Box-folder 5: 3)
      - Goodloe, John D., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 4)
      - Gossett, Ed, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 5: 5)
      - Gott, Philip P., 1947-1949 (Box-folder 5: 6)
      - Grace, J. Peter, Jr., 1949-1953 (Box-folder 5: 7)
      - Grand, Gordon, Jr., 1953 (Box-folder 5: 8)
      - Greene, Ernest Woodruff, 1949 (Box-folder 5: 9)
      - Gregg, Hugh, 1952 (Box-folder 5: 10)
      - Gross, Ernest A., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 11)
      - Gustafson, Andrew F., 1948 (Box-folder 5: 12)
      - Hale, Frederick, 1949 (Box-folder 5: 13)
      - Halleck, Charles A., 1952 (Box-folder 5: 14)
      - Hare, Van Court M., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 15)
      - Harl, Maple T., 1947-1951 (Box-folder 5: 16)
      - Harnett, Arthur J., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 17)
      - Harwood, Herbert H., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 18)
      - Hawkes, Albert W., 1948 (Box-folder 5: 19)
      - Haymes, P. L., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 20)
      - Heath, Andrew M., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 21)
      - Heide, Herman L., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 22)
      - Heimlich, Marion L., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 23)
      - Herndon, Roy L., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 24)
      - Hibben, Robert C., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 25)
      - Hill, Richard L., undated (Box-folder 5: 26)
      - Holloway, W. G., 1952 (Box-folder 5: 27)
      - Howrey, Edward F., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 28)
      - Huertematte, Roberto, 1952 (Box-folder 5: 29)
      - Huntington, Ellery C., Jr., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 30)
      - Johnston, Victor A., 1948 (Box-folder 5: 31)
      - Jurado, Jorge, 1951 (Box-folder 5: 32)
      - Kelly, Eugene, 1947 (Box-folder 5: 33)
      - Kent, Frank R., 1950 (Box-folder 5: 34)
      - Land, E. S., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 35)
      - Land, Mrs. E. S., 1950 (Box-folder 5: 36)
      - Lanham, Henderson, 1951 (Box-folder 5: 37)
      - Levy, Philip, 1947 (Box-folder 5: 38)
      - Lodge, John Davis, 1950 (Box-folder 5: 39)
      - Lustig, Harry, 1949 (Box-folder 5: 40)
      - Lutz, E. Russell, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 5: 41)
      - McCann, Lee, 1953 (Box-folder 5: 42)
      - McDaniel, Glen, 1951 (Box-folder 5: 43)
      - Macdonald, Godfrey, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 5: 44)
      - McDonald, Harry A., 1947-1952 (Box-folder 5: 45)
      - McFall, Jack K., 1948-1949 (Box-folder 5: 46)
      - McIntyre, Stanley L., 1950 (Box-folder 5: 47)
      - Mack, Walter S., Jr., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 48)
      - McKinnon, Clinton D., 1952 (Box-folder 5: 49)
      - McLaughlin, Ambrose P., 1951 (Box-folder 5: 50)
      - McLeod, Scott, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 5: 51)
      - Marshall, James H., 1948-1951 (Box-folder 5: 52)
      - Marvin, Langdon P., 1948 (Box-folder 5: 53)
      - Marvin, Langdon P., Jr., 1948-1949 (Box-folder 5: 54)
      - Mason, George G., 1950 (Box-folder 5: 55)
      - Merrell, George R., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 56)
      - Merrick, Robert G., 1950 (Box-folder 5: 57)
      - Merrow, Chester E., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 58)
      - Miller, J., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 59)
      - Morris, Edgar, 1951 (Box-folder 5: 60)
      - Morrison, Kenneth D., 1952 (Box-folder 5: 61)
      - Moscoso, Alfonso, 1952 (Box-folder 5: 62)
      - Multer, Abraham J., 1951-1952 (Box-folder 5: 63)
      - Myers, Lawrence, 1949 (Box-folder 5: 64)
      - Nelson, Herbert U., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 65)
      - Nieto del Rio, Felix, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 5: 66)
      - Nixon, Robert G., 1950 (Box-folder 5: 67)
      - Nyrop, Donald W., 1952 (Box-folder 5: 68)
      - O'Dunne, Eugene, Jr., 1952-1953 (Box-folder 5: 69)
      - Oehlert, Benjamin H., Jr., 1949-1952 (Box-folder 5: 70)
      - Pace, Frank, Jr., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 71)
      - Pareja Diezcanseco, Alfredo, 1951 (Box-folder 5: 72)
      - Parker, Kenneth C., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 73)
      - Parrott, Mae A., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 74)
      - Partridge, Daniel, III, 1949 (Box-folder 5: 75)
      - Patchin, R. H., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 76)
      - Pearson, H. A. M., 1951 (Box-folder 5: 77)
      - Quinlan, William A., 1947-1949 (Box-folder 5: 78)
      - Reece, Carroll, 1952 (Box-folder 5: 79)
      - Reilly, J. D., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 80)
      - Rentzel, D. W., 1952 (Box-folder 5: 81)
      - Restrepo Jaramillo, Cipriano, 1952 (Box-folder 5: 82)
      - Richards, James P., 1952 (Box-folder 5: 83)
      - Richardson, Seth W., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 84)
      - Riley, Earl, 1947 (Box-folder 5: 85)
      - Rimanoczy, Richard Stanton, 1953 (Box-folder 5: 86)
      - Robinson, Elwood J., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 87)
      - Sander, Charles F., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 88)
      - Saunders, William K., 1953 (Box-folder 5: 89)
      - Schreiber, W. R., 1953 (Box-folder 5: 90)
      - Scott, Hardie, 1952 (Box-folder 5: 91)
      - Shea, Andrew B., 1950-1953 (Box-folder 5: 92)
      - Shenton, Enoch, II, 1948 (Box-folder 5: 93)
      - Shields, Robert H., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 94)
      - Shoup, Merrill E., 1951 (Box-folder 5: 95)
      - Sides, Andrew B., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 96)
      - Sigma Nu Phi Fraternity, 1947 (Box-folder 5: 97)
      - Smith, C. Alfonso, 1952 (Box-folder 5: 98)
      - Smith, Dudley, 1949 (Box-folder 5: 99)
      - Smith, Frederick, 1948 (Box-folder 5: 100)
      - Smith, Harold O., Jr., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 101)
      - Sowder, Richard D., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 102)
      - Sparkman, John, 1947-1952 (Box-folder 5: 103)
      - Spingarn, Jerome H., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 104)
      - Spingarn, Stephen J., 1950 (Box-folder 5: 105)
      - Stark, J. E., 1949 (Box-folder 5: 106)
      - Stebbins, James H., 1948-1951 (Box-folder 5: 107)
      - Steinberg, Ceil, 1947 (Box-folder 5: 108)
      - Stempfel, Theodore, 1948 (Box-folder 5: 109)
      - Stevens, Lewis M., 1948 (Box-folder 5: 110)
      - Stewart, Grace, 1949 (Box-folder 5: 111)
      - Stockman, Lowell, 1952 (Box-folder 5: 112)
      - Thurston, Elliott, 1947 (Box-folder 5: 113)
      - Tobey, Charles W., 1947-1953 (Box-folder 5: 114)
      - Tobey, Russell, 1947 (Box-folder 5: 115)
      - Tydings, Millard E., 1950-1951 (Box-folder 5: 116)
      - Unidentified, 1948-1953 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - U.S. Comptroller of the Currency, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 2)
      - U.S. Department of State. Division of Foreign Service Personnel, 1947 (Box-folder 6: 3)
      - U.S. Department of State. Division of Publications, 1947 (Box-folder 6: 4)
      - U.S. Internal Revenue Service, 1953 (Box-folder 6: 5)
      - Upham, C. B., 1947 (Box-folder 6: 6)
      - Vandenberg, Arthur H., 1949 (Box-folder 6: 7)
      - Varma, S. N., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 6: 8)
      - Wadsworth, James W., 1950 (Box-folder 6: 9)
      - Wallach, Philip, 1949 (Box-folder 6: 10)
      - Wass, Dewey S., 1947 (Box-folder 6: 11)
      - Weinfeld, Edward, 1947 (Box-folder 6: 12)
      - Werner, Victor Davis, 1947 (Box-folder 6: 13)
      - Whitson, Robert D., 1952 (Box-folder 6: 14)
      - Wight, Willard, 1949 (Box-folder 6: 15)
      - Wilbur, Brayton, 1952 (Box-folder 6: 16)
      - Wilson, William L., 1947 (Box-folder 6: 17)
      - Wozencraft, Frank W., 1947 (Box-folder 6: 18)
      - Wythe, George, 1952 (Box-folder 6: 19)
    - Outgoing, 1947-1953
      - 1947
        - October (Box-folder 6: 20)
        - November (Box-folder 6: 21)
        - December (Box-folder 6: 22)
      - 1948
        - January (Box-folder 6: 23)
        - February (Box-folder 6: 24)
        - March (Box-folder 6: 25)
        - April (Box-folder 6: 26)
        - May (Box-folder 6: 27)
        - June (Box-folder 6: 28)
        - July (Box-folder 6: 29)
        - August (Box-folder 6: 30)
        - September (Box-folder 6: 31)
        - October (Box-folder 7: 1)
        - November (Box-folder 7: 2)
        - December (Box-folder 7: 3)
      - 1949
        - January (Box-folder 7: 4)
        - February (Box-folder 7: 5)
        - March (Box-folder 7: 6)
        - April (Box-folder 7: 7)
        - May (Box-folder 7: 8)
        - June (Box-folder 7: 9)
        - September (Box-folder 7: 10)
        - October (Box-folder 7: 11)
        - November (Box-folder 8: 1)
        - December (Box-folder 8: 2)
      - 1950
        - January (Box-folder 8: 3)
        - February (Box-folder 8: 4)
        - March (Box-folder 8: 5)
        - April (Box-folder 8: 6)
        - May (Box-folder 8: 7)
        - June (Box-folder 8: 8)
        - July (Box-folder 8: 9)
        - August (Box-folder 8: 10)
        - September (Box-folder 8: 11)
        - October (Box-folder 8: 12)
        - November (Box-folder 8: 13)
        - December (Box-folder 8: 14)
      - 1951
        - January (Box-folder 9: 1)
        - February (Box-folder 9: 2)
        - March (Box-folder 9: 3)
        - April (Box-folder 9: 4)
        - May (Box-folder 9: 5)
        - June (Box-folder 9: 6)
        - July (Box-folder 9: 7)
        - August (Box-folder 9: 8)
        - September (Box-folder 9: 9)
        - October (Box-folder 9: 10)
        - November (Box-folder 9: 11)
        - December (Box-folder 9: 12)
      - 1952
        - January (Box-folder 9: 13)